[
  { "question": "ناروتو", "answer": "ناروتو" },
  { "question": "شادو عمك", "answer": "شادو عمك" },
  { "question": "ارليكينو", "answer": "ارليكينو" },
  { "question": "الهيثم", "answer": "الهيثم" },
  { "question": "هيرو", "answer": "هيرو" },
  { "question": "هوليا", "answer": "هوليا" },
  { "question": "هيرا", "answer": "هيرا" },
  { "question": "هيستوريا", "answer": "هيستوريا" },
  { "question": "هومورا", "answer": "هومورا" },
  { "question": "هيماواري", "answer": "هيماواري" },
  { "question": "جاكس", "answer": "جاكس" },
  { "question": "جيمي", "answer": "جيمي" },
  { "question": "سيبر", "answer": "سيبر" },
  { "question": "جان", "answer": "جان" },
  { "question": "جيرايا", "answer": "جيرايا" },
  { "question": "يوميكو", "answer": "يوميكو" },
  { "question": "شوكو", "answer": "شوكو" },
  { "question": "ايري", "answer": "ايري" },
  { "question": "لولوش", "answer": "لولوش" },
  { "question": "اثي", "answer": "اثي" },
  { "question": "يوتا", "answer": "يوتا" },
  { "question": "فيودور", "answer": "فيودور" },
  { "question": "دازاي", "answer": "دازاي" },
  { "question": "اوتا", "answer": "اوتا" },
  { "question": "سانجي", "answer": "سانجي" },
  { "question": "ريكا", "answer": "ريكا" },
  { "question": "باغي", "answer": "باغي" },
  { "question": "ميراجين", "answer": "ميراجين" },
  { "question": "زورو", "answer": "زورو" },
  { "question": "ميرو", "answer": "ميرو" },
  { "question": "ريكي", "answer": "ريكي" },
  { "question": "نيشيميا", "answer": "نيشيميا" },
  { "question": "سيرينا", "answer": "سيرينا" },
  { "question": "كانيكي", "answer": "كانيكي" },
  { "question": "زينيتسو", "answer": "زينيتسو" },
  { "question": "نيزوكو", "answer": "نيزوكو" },
  { "question": "تانجيرو", "answer": "تانجيرو" },
  { "question": "روبي", "answer": "روبي" },
  { "question": "آي", "answer": "آي" },
  { "question": "ال", "answer": "ال" },
  { "question": "لايت", "answer": "لايت" },
  { "question": "لوفي", "answer": "لوفي" },
  { "question": "روبين", "answer": "روبين" },
  { "question": "نامي", "answer": "نامي" },
  { "question": "مادارا", "answer": "مادارا" },
  { "question": "ميكو", "answer": "ميكو" },
  { "question": "انجيلو", "answer": "انجيلو" },
  { "question": "اكاي", "answer": "اكاي" },
  { "question": "كونان", "answer": "كونان" },
  { "question": "تاكوما", "answer": "تاكوما" },
  { "question": "سوسكي", "answer": "سوسكي" },
  { "question": "يونا", "answer": "يونا" },
  { "question": "رين", "answer": "رين" },
  { "question": "هيناتا", "answer": "هيناتا" },
  { "question": "كيبا", "answer": "كيبا" },
  { "question": "ساكورا", "answer": "ساكورا" },
  { "question": "شينسو", "answer": "شينسو" },
  { "question": "ميليدايس", "answer": "ميليدايس" }
]
